mvn.com 2018-01-15

# Privacy Policy - MVN Associates, Inc.

## Privacy Policy

**MVN ASSOCIATES PRIVACY POLICY**  
MVN Associates (MVN) has created this privacy policy because we value our customers and recognize their right to keep personal information private. This statement discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this MVN website, which may be updated by us from time to time without notice to you.

**MVN GATHERS THE FOLLOWING INFORMATION:  
IP Address & Web Browser Info**  
MVN’s web servers and forms on the web gather your IP address and Web browser type to help diagnose problems with our service, to administer our site, and to gather broad demographic information. Demographic information is gathered in aggregate only and cannot be traced to an individual user.

**Cookies**  
MVN’s website sets cookies to keep track of advertising banner ad hits and other similar information. MVN's web servers may also set a session ID cookie that is used to allow our servers to deliver information you request (e.g., search results). Session IDs cannot be traced to an individual person or customer name, and are analyzed only in aggregate. Members who do not want to receive cookies can instruct their web browsers to refuse them; be aware, however, that doing so may prevent certain parts of MVN's site from working. Other organizations which place advertising on MVN sometimes have the ability to assign a different cookie to you in a process that we do not control. Unless you've saved your customer name, cookies aren't useable for identifying individuals (your computer will be assigned a random number); neither MVN nor advertisers will know who you are.

**PROTECTION OF CHILDREN**  
Consistent with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998, we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. If we become aware that a subscriber is under the age of 13 and has signed up without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files.

**OFF SITE LINKS**  
MVN provides links to other sites. MVN is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these Web sites.

**YOUR PRIVATE ONLINE COMMUNICATIONS**  
MVN believes that customer's private communications in email and other methods of communication should remain confidential. MVN does not read or disclose private communications unless ordered to do so through a valid legal mechanism such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order, to protect the company's rights and property, or during emergencies when we believe physical safety is at risk. Also, keep in mind that MVN is not responsible for what other users may do with private communications you've had with them.

**CONTACTING US**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, you can contact us at:  
1\. Via email:   [dmac@mvnassociates.com](mailto:dmac@mvnassociates.com)  
2\. Via web:  our Contact Us section
